adblade.com 2019-12-29

# Adblade - Privacy Policy

Overview

Adblade.com and its network of owned and partnered publishers ("Adblade") places importance on the privacy of our clients and their businesses. We adhere to the policies regarding privacy and security outlined below. If you have any questions, comments or concerns, please do not hesitate to contact us at [privacy@adblade.com](mailto:privacy@adblade.com) Please familiarize yourself with the policies that are applicable to you.

Adblade Privacy Policy

Adblade Advertisers

If an individual or business chooses to sign up as an advertiser on the Adblade Premium Advertising Network, they are explicitly agreeing to the use of information they provide as described below. The nature of this technology means that advertisers who do not agree with this policy cannot use the Adblade Premium Advertising Network, advertising interface or measurement tools. The Terms and Conditions that they agree to during registration allow Adblade to update the terms of this privacy policy at any time and without notice. It is an Advertiser's responsibility to review this privacy policy prior to logging in. Use of Adblade is conditioned on advertiser’s acceptance without modification of the terms, conditions, and notices contained herein. Use of the Adblade Premium Advertising Network constitutes your agreement to all such terms, conditions, and notices.

Personal information provided by an advertiser will be combined with information about its purchasing patterns of Adblade's products and services, performance of its advertisements, and all other information provided by the advertiser. Adblade regularly shares this information with key partners on an individual basis. Furthermore, Adblade and its partners may use this information to contact the advertiser about additional products and services.

An advertiser has the right to terminate their relationship with Adblade in accordance with the terms and conditions set forth in the advertiser's contract with Adblade. However, all information captured about the advertiser will remain the property of Adblade indefinitely.

Adblade AdNetwork Privacy Policy

Ad Serving

Adblade partners with numerous companies to provide online advertisements to "End Users" which are human users across various websites on the internet. As an End User browses the web, he or she may visit web-pages that include references to Adblade's advertising service. When this happens, an End User's browser may request advertisements from Adblade's system.

When Adblade receives these requests from non-European Union (EU) countries, we may record information about this interaction (as well as any further interaction with our advertisements such as clicks, mouse movements, etc.) including the End User's IP address and time of request, information about the general geographical location from which an End User is viewing an advertisement and other information made available by the browser. For EU countries, Adblade does not store any personally identifiable information, makes no attempt to identify anyone personally, and does not target any ads based on any of these factors.

Additionally, Adblade employs small text files stored on your web browser (otherwise known as cookies) for the purpose of better tailoring advertisements to an End User's preferences over time. These cookies may include a unique anonymous identifier along with information about the particular types of content in which the End User has shown interest.

On occasion, partner sites, vendors or internally run surveys may provide us with additional information about End Users. In these situations, all information is kept entirely anonymous and does not include any type of personally identifiable information. Adblade only accepts this information from organizations with clearly available and visible privacy policies.

Adblade does not sell information it collects about End Users. However, Adblade may share data about aggregate usage statistics with the public or other businesses with whom we work.

The capture, storage and analysis of information are solely for the purposes of ensuring a positive End User experience, eliminating fraudulent activity, and system administration.

Organizations We Work With

Adblade provides access to organizations we work with on Adblade's Premium Advertising Network to manage their own advertising networks. Those relationships are managed under contracts between Adblade and the respective partners. The campaign management tools which Adblade provides to many of its partners allow each such partner to view all relevant information of Adblade's advertisers whose ads are being displayed on that partner's site. Such information includes bidding data, spend data, topics and placements viewed and purchased.

General Privacy Policy

Adblade Targeted Advertising and How to Opt-out

"Cookies" are small data files that are sent to your browser and are stored on your hard drive, keeping track of your general activity on a site. When you make subsequent visits to our site or another site on our Advertising Network, your cookie gives us a summary of your preferences and past experiences on the site. This allows us to tailor Adblade services to your needs. Your cookie may be altered at different times throughout your visits to a site, and it is updated frequently as you use various Adblade features and services. We keep different data for different lengths of time. Include/Exclude Segment Categories (1 year). Ad Clicker (2 years). Conversion Cookie (1 month). Frequency Cap (varies by advertiser). Impression/Click Validator (Immediate). All server data is kept for 2 years and contains no personally identifiable information. All data is deleted at the end of relevant period.

Every time you use Adblade services, our server may deliver certain customized information to you based on the data stored in your cookie. You may opt-out of our cookie-based targeted advertising. Click here to view/change your preferences for the Adblade Targeted Advertising program. Adblade shall retain data collected and used for these activities only as long as necessary to fulfill a legitimate business need, or as required by law. We comply with the [FTC Online Behavioral Advertising Principles](https://www.ftc.gov/sites/default/files/documents/reports/federal-trade-commission-staff-report-self-regulatory-principles-online-behavioral-advertising/p085400behavadreport.pdf).

We may use third party advertising technology providers to serve advertisements and provide other services on this site and in connection with our Advertising Network. These services may include the use of web beacons, web bugs, action tags and third party cookies which read our cookies, or visa-versa, or involve the use of anonymous supplemental information (described below). 

"Clickstream data" is a trail of electronic information that is left at each web site you visit. This information can be collected and stored by a site's server. We may, for example, use clickstream data to tell us the type of computer and browsing software you use, the address of the site from which you encountered Adblade Advertisements, how much time you spend on each page of our site, how you navigate throughout the site and how we may tailor our web pages to better meet the needs of our users. To opt out of the Adblade Targeting Program, your browser must be set to accept cookies. If you clear your browser's cookies, you may need to opt out again.

Data Security

We have implemented reasonable security measures to protect the information in our care, both during transmission and once we receive it. This includes, but is not limited to, the use of firewalls and encryption. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

Conclusion

Adblade works hard to respect the privacy of its users. Unless required otherwise by applicable law or legal process, Adblade will operate entirely within the policies described above. If you have any questions or concerns regarding this policy, please feel free to contact [privacy@adblade.com](mailto:privacy@adblade.com)

Adblade reserves the right to change this policy at any time due to changes in applicable laws, Adblade's business needs or otherwise. Use of Adblade.com and the advertising network of owned and partnered websites which utilize Adblade's services constitute agreement with the terms of this policy as may be amended by Adblade from time to time.

Last updated: September 22, 2015
